Guide to the Investment Committee, Yale University, Records of Meetings
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Investment Committee, Yale University, records of meetings
1988-2005
RU 297
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
4.55
6 boxes
1022
The records consist of meeting agendas and minutes, reports, and materials of the Investment Committee maintained by the Yale Investment Office.
Yale University. Investment Office
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 5-D (YRG 5-D), Investment and insurance records of Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of meeting agendas and minutes, reports, and materials of the Investment Committee maintained by the Yale Investment Office.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Investments; Universities and colleges -- Finance; Yale University -- Finance; Yale University. Investment Office; Yale University. Office of Finance and Administration
- Investment Committee Reports, 1988-1996; Accession 1997-A-043
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2046.
  - 1988 Sep (Box 1)
  - 1988 Dec (Box 1)
  - 1989 Mar (Box 1)
  - 1989 Jun (Box 1)
  - 1989 Oct (Box 1)
  - 1990 Jan (Box 1)
  - 1990 Mar (Box 1)
  - 1990 Jun (Box 1)
  - 1990 Oct (Box 1)
  - 1990 Dec (Box 1)
  - 1991 Mar (Box 1)
  - 1991 Jun (Box 1)
  - 1991 Oct (Box 2)
  - 1992 Jan (Box 2)
  - 1992 Mar (Box 2)
  - 1992 Jun (Box 2)
  - 1992 Sep (Box 2)
  - 1993 Jan (Box 2)
  - 1993 Mar (Box 2)
  - 1993 Jun (Box 2)
  - 1993 Oct (Box 2)
  - 1994 Jun (Box 2)
  - 1995 Jan (Box 3)
  - 1995 Mar (Box 3)
  - 1995 Jun (executive summary only) (Box 4)
  - 1995 Sep (Box 4)
  - 1996 Mar (Box 4)
  - 1996 Jul (Box 4)
- Minutes, agendas, and reports of the Investment Committee [computer files], 1975-2000; Accession 2001-A-026
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2050.
  Scope and Contents
  For the most part, each file on the CDs represents either a quarterly mailing or annual report from the Investment Office to the Investment Committee for the period 1975 to March 2000. These mailings have followed a standard format since 1985, and the pdf files covering these years are exact copies of the original documents. The material prior to 1985 has been recreated from incomplete records as best as we were able to follow the format of the later reports; this revision is noted on the title page of the early-period documents. There are a couple of additional files that represent interim mailings to the Committee and special reports on Endowment investment performance.
  Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
  - Original Disks
    - IC Meetings 2000-1989 Volume 1, 2001-a-026-0001; 1 (Box 1)
    - IC Meetings 1988-1975 Volume 2, 2001-a-026-0002; 1 (Box 2)
  - Files Processed from Disks
    - Meetings
      - 1996 Dec, computer file (PDF)
        General note
        Contact Public Services (phone: 203 432-1735, e-mail: mssa.reference@yale.edu) for information on accessing this digital object.
      - 1997 Apr, computer file (PDF)
      - 1990 Dec, computer file (PDF)
      - 1993 Dec, computer file (PDF)
      - 1997 Dec, computer file (PDF)
      - 1998 Dec, computer file (PDF)
      - 1999 Dec, computer file (PDF)
      - 1990 Jan, computer file (PDF)
      - 1992 Jan, computer file (PDF)
      - 1993 Jan, computer file (PDF)
      - 1995, computer file (PDF)
      - 1996 Jan, computer file (PDF)
      - 1996 Jul, computer file (PDF)
      - 1989 Jun, computer file (PDF)
      - 1990 Jun, computer file (PDF)
      - 1991 Jun, computer file (PDF)
      - 1992 Jun, computer file (PDF)
      - 1993 Jun, computer file (PDF)
      - 1994 Jun, computer file (PDF)
      - 1995 Jun, computer file (PDF)
      - 1997 Jun, computer file (PDF)
      - 1998 Jun, computer file (PDF)
      - 1999 Jun, computer file (PDF)
      - 1989 Mar, computer file (PDF)
      - 1991 Mar, computer file (PDF)
      - 1992 Mar, computer file (PDF)
      - 1993 Mar, computer file (PDF)
      - 1994 Mar, computer file (PDF)
      - 1995 Mar, computer file (PDF)
      - 1996 Mar, computer file (PDF)
      - 1998 Mar, computer file (PDF)
      - 1999 Mar, computer file (PDF)
      - 2000 Mar, computer file (PDF)
      - 1989 Oct, computer file (PDF)
      - 1990 Oct, computer file (PDF)
      - 1991 Oct, computer file (PDF)
      - 1993 Oct, computer file (PDF)
      - 1994 Oct, computer file (PDF)
      - 1999 Oct, computer file (PDF)
      - 1992 Sep, computer file (PDF)
      - 1995 Sep, computer file (PDF)
      - 1996 Sep, computer file (PDF)
      - 1997 Sep, computer file (PDF)
    - Agendas and Minutes
      - 1978-1989, computer file (PDF)
      - 1990-1999, computer file (PDF)
    - Meetings
      - 1975, computer file (PDF)
      - 1976, computer file (PDF)
      - 1977, computer file (PDF)
      - 1987 Dec, computer file (PDF)
      - 1988 Dec, computer file (PDF)
      - 1986 Jun, computer file (PDF)
      - 1987 Jun, computer file (PDF)
      - 1988 Jun, computer file (PDF)
      - 1986 Mar, computer file (PDF)
      - 1987 Mar, computer file (PDF)
      - 1988 Mar, computer file (PDF)
      - 1986 Nov, computer file (PDF)
      - 1988 Sep, computer file (PDF)
      - 1978, computer file (PDF)
      - 1979, computer file (PDF)
      - 1980, computer file (PDF)
      - 1981, computer file (PDF)
      - 1982, computer file (PDF)
      - 1983, computer file (PDF)
      - 1984, computer file (PDF)
- Bound minutes, agendas & meeting notes of the Yale University Investments Committee, 2004-2005; Accession 2006-A-138
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2055.